Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on Trade Unions PE.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- I, 1884-2010; 15 Linear Feet in 14 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, and 2 oversize shared boxes
  - International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Salaried, Machine and Furniture Workers: Local 301 (Schenectady, NY), 1987 (Box 26)
  - International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Technical, Salaried and Machine Workers: Local 450, 1982, undated (Box 26)
  - International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Technical, Salaried and Machine Workers: Local 470, 1982 (Box 26)
  - International Union of Elevator Constructors, 1956, 1961, 1984 (Box 26)
  - International Union of Food and Allied Workers' Associations, 1962-1963, 1988-1989 (Box 26)
  - International Union of Gas Workers, undated (Box 26)
  - International Union of Hotel, Restaurant and Bar-workers, 1951 (Box 26)
  - International Union of Journeymen Horseshoers of the United States and Canada, 1942, 1977 (Box 26)
  - International Union of Male and Female Workers Employed in the Food and Drink Trades, 1926 (Box 26)
  - International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, 1940-1947 (Box 26)
  - International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, 1955-1963, undated (Box 26)
  - International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers: Constitutions and By-Laws, 1940-1946 (Box 26)
  - International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers: Local 489 (Treece, KS), 1944-1946 (Box 26)
  - International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers: Local 671 (Picher, OK), 1943 (Box 26)
  - International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers: Local 856, 1946 (Box 26)
  - International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers: Local 861, 1946 (Box 26)
  - International Union of Operating Engineers, 1940 (Box 26)
  - International Union of Operating Engineers, 1968-1969 (Box 26)
  - International Union of Operating Engineers, 1971-1974 (Box 26)
  - International Union of Operating Engineers: Agreements (Various Locals), 1967-1983, undated (Box 26)
  - International Union of Operating Engineers: Constitutions, 1938-1964 (Box 26)
  - International Union of Operating Engineers: Constitutions, 1972-1988 (Box 26)
  - International Union of Operating Engineers: Local 94, 1984 (Box 26)
  - International Union of Operating Engineers: Local 891 (New York, NY), 1982, 1988 (Box 26)
  - International Union of Petroleum and Industrial Workers, 1977, undated (Box 26)
  - International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers of America, 1950-1961, undated (Box 26)
  - International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers of America: Local 9 (Milwaukee, WI), 1961, undated (Box 26)
  - International Union of Woodworkers, 1927 (Box 26)
  - International Upholsterers Union of North America, undated (Box 26)
  - International Woodcarvers' Association of North America, 1896 (Box 26)
  - International Woodcarvers' Association: Rochester Branch (Rochester, NY), 1897 (Box 26)
  - International Woodworkers of America, 1944-1978, undated (Box 26)
  - International Woodworkers of America: Constitutions, 1959-1979 (Box 26)
  - International Workers Order, 1935-1953, undated (Box 26, Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Internationale Buchbinder Foderation, 1923 (Box 26)
  - Iowa Union Farmer Association, circa 1953 (Box 26)
  - Irish Trade Union Congress, 1952 (Box 26)
  - Irish Transport and General Workers Union, 1924-1982, undated (Box 27)
  - Iron Molders' Union of North America, 1890-1918 (Box 27)
  - Iron Molders' Union of North America: Number 292 (Machinery Molders Union, Albany, NY), 1900 (Box 27)
  - Iron Workers Welfare Plan of Eastern Ohio, 1959 (Box 27)
  - Italian Women's Union (Unione Donne Italiane), undated (Box 27)
- J, 1819-1989; 1 linear foot in 1 record carton
  - Japanese Trade Union Confederation (REGNO), 1989, undated (Box 27)
  - Jewelers' Protective Union, 1899 (Box 27)
  - Joint Industry Board of the Electrical Industry, 1949-1974 (Box 27)
  - Joint Industry Board of the Electrical Industry, 1980-1981, undated (Box 27)
  - Joint Plumbing Industry Board, 1958, undated (Box 27)
  - Journeymen Bakers' and Confectioners' International Union, undated (Box 27)
  - Journeymen Bakers' and Confectioners' International Union: Constitution and Membership Book, 1899, 1901 (Box 27)
  - Journeymen Bakers' and Confectioners' International Union: Local Union No. 50 (New York, NY), 1900 (Box 27)
  - Journeymen Barbers', Cosmetologists, and Hairdressers International Union of America: Local 151 (Buffalo, NY), 1963-1964 (Box 27)
  - Journeymen Barbers', Hairdressers and Cosmetologists International Union of America, 1938-1942, undated (Box 27)
  - Journeymen Barbers', Hairdressers, Cosmetologists, and Proprietors International Union of America, 1954-1972, undated (Box 27)
  - Journeymen Barbers' International Union of America, 1893, undated (Box 27)
  - Journeymen Barbers' International Union of America: Local 168 (Oneonta, NY), 1894 (Box 27)
  - Journeymen Horseshoers' Protective Union and Benevolent Society, undated (Box 27)
  - Journeymen Horseshoers' Protective Union and Benevolent Society of the City and County of New York, 1872 (Box 27)
  - Journeymen Horseshoers' Protective Union and Benevolent Society of the City of Brooklyn, NY, 1886 (Box 27)
  - Journeymen Horseshoers' Protective Union and Benevolent Society of the City of Buffalo, NY, 1884 (Box 27)
  - Journeymen Stonecutters Association of North America, 1924, 1929, 1957 (Box 27)
  - Journeymen Tailors' Union of North America, 1819, 1892-1917 (Box 27)
- K, 1897; 1 Linear Feet in 1 record carton
  - Kane Labor League (Kane, PA), 1897 (Box 27)
- L, 1890-2008; 1 linear foot in 1 record carton
  - Labor Council for Latin American Advancement, 1978 (Box 27)
  - Labor Press Council of Metropolitan New York, 1981-1993 (Box 27)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America, 1979-1980 (Box 27)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America, 1981-2004, undated (Box 27)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America: Agreements, 1984-1993 (Box 27)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America: Alaska State District Council of Laborers, 1977-1978 (Box 27)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America: Constitutions, 1966-1988 (Box 27)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America: Local 78 (flier), undated (Box 27)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America: Local 79 (Construction and General Building Laborers, New York, NY), 2008 (Box 27)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America: Local 118 (Evanston, IL), 1973 (Box 27)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America: National Post Office Mail Handlers, Watchmen, Messengers and Group Leaders Division, 1980 (Box 27)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America: National Post Office Mail Handlers Union, 1988-1990 (Box 27)
  - Ladies' Waist-Maker's Union: Shirt-waist Maker's Strike of 1909, 1909-1910, 1982, undated; photocopies and reprints of originals (Box 27)
  - Latin American Confederation of Labor, 1942-1944 (Box 27)
  - Laundry Workers International Union, 1940-1941 (Box 27)
  - Laundry Workers' Joint Organizing Committee, undated (Box 27)
  - Laundry Workers' Union: Local 66, undated (Box 27)
  - Lasters' Protective Union, 1890 (Box 27)
  - League of Off-Broadway Theatrical Employees and Technicians, undated (Box 27)
  - Leather Workers International Union of America, 1962 (Box 27)
  - Legal Services Staff Association, undated (Box 27)
  - Library Employees' Union of Greater New York, 1919 (Box 27)
  - Lieutenants Benevolent Association, 1955 (Box 27)
  - Lithographers and Photoengravers International Union, 1964, undated (Box 27)
  - Lithographers and Photoengravers International Union: Local 1-P (New York, NY), 1967-1978 (Box 27)
  - Longshoremens Benevolent and Civic Association, 1962 (Box 27)
  - Louisiana Farmers' Union, 1937-1939 (Box 27)
- M, 1925-2002; 2 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons
  - Major League Players Association, 1958-1985 (Box 27)
  - Manchester and Salford Trades Council, 1930 (Box 27)
  - Marine Cooks and Stewards Association of the Pacific Coast, 1941 (Box 27)
  - Marine Cooks and Stewards Association of the Pacific Coast, 1944 (Box 27)
  - Marine Cooks and Stewards Association of the Pacific Coast I, 1945 (Box 28)
  - Marine Cooks and Stewards Association of the Pacific Coast II, 1945 (Box 28)
  - Marine Cooks and Stewards Association of the Pacific Coast III, 1945 (Box 28)
  - Marine Cooks and Stewards Association of the Pacific Coast, 1946-1951, undated (Box 28)
  - Marine Draftsmen's Association, 1944 (Box 28)
  - Marine Firemen's Union, 1952-1977 (Box 28)
  - Marine Workers Industrial Union, 1934 (Box 28)
  - Maritime Federation of the Pacific, 1940 (Box 28)
  - Maritime Industry: Strikes and Struggles, 1936-1961, undated (Box 28)
  - Massachusetts Trade Union Educational League, 1979 (Box 28)
  - Master Steam and Hot Water Fitters' Association (Brooklyn, NY), undated (Box 28)
  - Mechanics Educational Society of America: Constitution and By-laws, 1979 (Box 28)
  - Metal Polishers, Buffers, Platers and Helpers International Union, 1943, 1952 (Box 28)
  - Metal Spinners and Silver Plated Hollow-ware Workers Union, 1957 (Box 28)
  - Metal Workers Union (Brazil), 1986 (Box 28)
  - Metro New York Labor Communications Council, 1997-2002, undated (Box 28)
  - Milk Wagon Drivers Unions of Greater Boston Local 380, undated (Box 28)
  - Miners' Federation of Great Britain I, 1925-1927, undated (Box 28)
  - Miners' Federation of Great Britain II, 1925-1927, undated (Box 28)
  - Musicians' Union (Great Britain), 1947 (Box 28)
- N, 1875-2007; 5.5 Linear Feet in 5 record cartons and 1 manuscript box
  - National Afro-American Labor Council, 1972 (Box 28)
  - National Agricultural Workers Union, 1959, undated (Box 28)
  - National Alliance of Postal Employees: Brooklyn Branch, 1950 (Box 28)
  - National Amalgamated Society of Operative House and Ship Painters and Decorators (Great Britain), undated (Box 28)
  - National Amalgamated Union of Labour (Great Britain), 1918-1921 (Box 28)
  - National Association of Die Casting Workers, 1940 (Box 28)
  - National Association of Engineers: Number 3 (Rochester, NY), 1883 (Box 28)
  - National Association of Letter Carriers, 1964-1997, undated (Box 28)
  - National Association of Letter Carriers: Agreements and Contracts, 1970-1987 (Box 28)
  - National Association of Letter Carriers: Branch 36 (New York, NY), 1970, 1983-1984 (Box 28)
  - National Association of Letter Carriers: Constitutions and By-Laws, 1943-1976 (Box 28)
  - National Association of Letter Carriers: Constitutions and By-Laws, 1978-1994 (Box 28)
  - National Association of Postal Supervisors, 1978 (Box 28)
  - National Association of Special Delivery Messengers of the U.S. Postal Service, 1939 (Box 28)
  - National Association of Substitute Post Office Employees, undated (Box 28)
  - National Association of Wool Manufacturers, 1895 (Box 28)
  - National Education Association, 1914-1937 (Box 28)
  - National Education Association, 1944-1948 (Box 28)
  - National Education Association, 1968-1971 (Box 28)
  - National Education Association, 1973 (Box 28)
  - National Education Association, 1975-1991, undated (Box 28)
  - National Education Association: Agreements, 1972-1973 (Box 29)
  - National Education Association: Constitutions and By-Laws, 1972-1981 (Box 29)
  - National Electrical Contractors Association (U.S.), 2001 (Box 29)
  - National Faculty Association of Community and Junior Colleges, undated (Box 29)
  - National Farm Labor Union (U.S.), 2003 (Box 29)
  - National Farmers' Union (Canada), 1973-1974, undated (Box 29)
  - National Farmers' Union (U.S.), 1955-1960 (Box 29)
  - National Farmers' Union (U.S.), 1969-1988, undated (Box 29)
  - National Farmers' Union Education Service, 1943-1944 (Box 29)
  - National Federation of Blastfurnacemen (Great Britain), 1897 (Box 29)
  - National Federation of Building Trades Operatives, 1942-1943 (Box 29)
  - National Federation of Federal Employees I, 1967-1978 (Box 29)
  - National Federation of Federal Employees II, 1967-1978 (Box 29)
  - National Federation of Independent Unions, undated (Box 29)
  - National Federation of Licensed Practical Nurses, Inc., 1989 (Box 29)
  - National Federation of Post Office Clerks, 1926-1960 (Box 29)
  - National Federation of Post Office Clerks: Constitutions, 1931-1952 (Box 29)
  - National Federation of Telephone Workers, 1938-1944 (Box 29, Box 49, Folder 12)
  - National Federation of Telephone Workers, 1942-1943 (Box 29)
  - National Federation of Telephone Workers, 1945 (Box 29)
  - National Federation of Telephone Workers I, 1946 (Box 29)
  - National Federation of Telephone Workers II, 1946 (Box 29)
  - National Federation of Telephone Workers III, 1946 (Box 29)
  - National Federation of Telephone Workers, 1947- (Box 29)
  - National Federation of Telephone Workers, undated (Box 29)
  - National Football League Players Association, 1974-1978 (Box 29)
  - National Football League Players Association, 1979-1982, undated (Box 29)
  - National Guilds League (Great Britain), 1921 (Box 29)
  - National Labor Committee, 1997, undated (Box 29)
  - National Labor Relations Review Board (NLRB), 1958, 1964 (Box 29)
  - National League for Nursing, 1967 (Box 29)
  - National League of Musicians of the United States: Local 69 (Musicians' Protective Union, Utica, NY), 1893-1897 (Box 29)
  - National Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association I, 1950-1975, undated (Box 30)
  - National Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association II, 1950-1975, undated (Box 30)
  - National Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association: Agreements, 1948-1951 (Box 30)
  - National Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association: Agreements: District 1, 1965-1987 (Box 30)
  - National Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association: Constitutions and By-Laws, 1936-1959 (Box 30)
  - National Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association: Constitutions and By-Laws, 1976-1989 (Box 30)
  - National Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association: History, 1950 (Box 30)
  - National Metal Workers Minority Movement (London, England), undated (Box 30)
  - National Miners' Union (U.S.), 1928, undated (Box 30)
  - National Organization of Masters, Mates and Pilots of America, 1913, 1940-1942 (Box 30)
  - National Postal Clerks Union, undated (Box 30)
  - National Rural Letter Carriers' Association, 1981 (Box 30)
  - National Seamen's Union (Israel), 1952 (Box 30)
  - National Seamen's Unity Convention, 1938 (Box 30)
  - National Trades Union Congress (Singapore), 1965 (Box 30)
  - National Textile Workers Union (U.S.), 1932-2003, undated (Box 30)
  - National Treasury Employees Union, 1967, 1979 (Box 30)
  - National Treasury Employees Union, 1982-1983 (Box 30)
  - National Union of Agricultural and Allied Workers (Great Britain), 1972 (Box 30)
  - National Union of Distributive and Allied Workers, 1937 (Box 30)
  - National Union of General and Municipal Workers (Great Britain), 1925 (Box 30)
  - National Union of General Workers Zenkoku-Ippan (Japan), 1990 (Box 30)
  - National Union of Journalists (Great Britain), 1975-1976, undated (Box 30)
  - National Union of Marine Cooks and Stewards, 1945-1946 (Box 30)
  - National Union of Marine Cooks and Stewards, 1948-1949 (Box 30)
  - National Union of Marine Cooks and Stewards, 1950-1951 (Box 30)
  - National Union of Marine Cooks and Stewards, 1953, undated (Box 30)
  - National Union of Mineworkers (Great Britain), 1980s, undated (Box 30)
  - National Union of Tailors and Garment Workers, 1938-1959, undated (Box 30)
  - National Window Glass Workers, 1914-1917 (Box 30)
  - National Women's Trade Union League of America, 1934-1947, undated (Box 30)
  - National Women's Trade Union League of North America, 1909-1929 (Box 30)
  - National Writers Union (U.S.), 1982-1996, undated (Box 30)
  - Needle Trade Workers Industrial Union, 1925-1932, undated (Box 31)
  - Needle Trade Workers Industrial Union: Fur Department, undated (Box 31)
  - New York Building Congress, 1977 (Box 31)
  - New York City Taxi Drivers Union, 1932, 1962-1975, undated (Box 31)
  - New York City Taxi Drivers Union: Agreements, 1970-1979 (Box 31)
  - New York City Taxi Drivers Union: Lease Drivers Benefit Fund, 1978-1985 (Box 31)
  - New York City Taxi Drivers Union: Rank and File I, 1966-1977 (Box 31)
  - New York City Taxi Drivers Union: Rank and File II, 1966-1977 (Box 31)
  - New York City Transit Employees Benevolent Association, 1942 (Box 31)
  - New York College Teachers Union: Brooklyn Chapter, undated (Box 31)
  - New York Electrical Workers Union, undated (Box 31)
  - New York Hotel and Motel Council, 1964-1969 (Box 31)
  - New York Hotel and Motel Council, 1974-1985, undated (Box 31)
  - New York Hotel and Motel Council: Collective Bargaining Agreements, 1966-1969 (Box 31)
  - New York Hotel and Motel Council: Collective Bargaining Agreements, 1972-1975 (Box 31)
  - New York Hotel and Motel Council: Collective Bargaining Agreements, 1978 (Box 31)
  - New York Hotel and Motel Council: Collective Bargaining Agreements, 1981 (Box 31)
  - New York Hotel Trades Council, 1939-1952 (Box 31)
  - New York Hotel Trades Council, 1955-1961, undated (Box 31)
  - New York Hotel Trades Council: Collective Bargaining Agreements, 1945-1949 (Box 31)
  - New York Hotel Trades Council: Collective Bargaining Agreements, 1951-1962 (Box 31)
  - New York Joint Dress Board, 1950 (Box 31)
  - New York Mailers' Union, 1954-1981 (Box 31)
  - New York Public Library Staff Association, 1917-1942 (Box 31)
  - New York State Federation of Post Office Clerks, 1945 (Box 31)
  - New York State Nurses Association, 1959-1975, undated (Box 31)
  - New York State Public Employees Federation, 1975-1985 (Box 31)
  - New York State Public Employees Federation, 1988-1991, undated (Box 31)
  - New York State United Teachers (NYUST), 1938-1942 (Box 31)
  - New York State United Teachers (NYUST), 1970-1975 (Box 31)
  - New York State United Teachers (NYUST), 1976-1978 (Box 32)
  - New York State United Teachers (NYUST), 1979-1982 (Box 32)
  - New York State United Teachers (NYUST), 1984-1989 (Box 32)
  - New York State United Teachers (NYUST), 1990-3002 (Box 32)
  - New York State United Teachers (NYUST), undated (Box 32)
  - New York Stereotyper's Association, 1875 (Box 32)
  - New York Subway Guild, 1954, undated (Box 32)
  - New York Teachers Guild, 1935-1955, undated (Box 32)
  - New Zealand Federation of Labour, 1949 (Box 32)
  - New York Taxi Workers Alliance, 2000-2007 (Box 32)
  - Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union of New York and Vicinity, 1937, 1944-1945 (Box 32)
  - Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union of New York and Vicinity: Agreements, 1935-1967 (Box 32)
  - Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union of New York and Vicinity: Agreements, 1970-1981 (Box 32)
  - North East Coast Allied Craftmens' Committee: Memorandum of Agreements, 1924 (Box 32)
  - Norwegian Confederation of Trade Unions (LO) (Landsorganisasjonen i Norge), 1998, undated (Box 32)
  - Norwegian National Federation of Trade Unions, 1948-1949 (Box 32)
- O, 1884-2004; 2 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons
  - Office and Professional Employees International Union, 1966-1978 (Box 32)
  - Office and Professional Employees International Union, 1980-1991 (Box 32)
  - Office and Professional Employees International Union, undated (Box 32)
  - Office and Professional Employees International Union: Local 2, 1968-1970 (Box 32)
  - Office and Professional Employees International Union: Local 3 (San Francisco, CA), undated (Box 32)
  - Office and Professional Employees International Union: Local 153 (New York, NY), 1969-2004 (Box 32)
  - Office and Professional Employees International Union: Local 153 (New York, NY), undated (Box 32)
  - Office Employees International Union, 1954-1959, undated (Box 32)
  - Office Employees International Union: Constitutions, 1942-1962 (Box 32)
  - Office Employees International Union: Local 42, 1958 (Box 32)
  - Office Employees International Union: Local 139 (San Diego, CA), undated (Box 32)
  - Office Employees International Union: Local 153 (New York, NY), 1947-1957 (Box 32)
  - Office Employees International Union: Local 153 (New York, NY), 1959-1971 (Box 32)
  - Office Employees International Union: Local 205, undated (Box 32)
  - Office Employees International Union: Local 344 (New York, NY), 1955-1957 (Box 32)
  - Office Employees International Union: Local 344 (New York, NY), 1957-1959, undated (Box 32)
  - Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, 1955-1974 (Box 32)
  - Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, 1975-2002, undated (Box 32)
  - Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union: Constitutional Convention, 1956 (Box 32)
  - Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union: Constitutions, 1955-1977 (Box 33)
  - Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union: District 8, 1983, undated (Box 33)
  - Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union: Hazards in the Industrial Environment, 1969 (Box 33)
  - Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union: Hazards in the Industrial Environment, 1970 (Box 33)
  - Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union: Health and Safety, 1972-1973 (Box 33)
  - Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union: Industrial Hazards, 1971 (Box 33)
  - Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union: "Labor Party Advocates" Publications, 1993-1996 (Box 33)
  - Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union: Research and Education Department, 1974, undated (Box 33)
  - Oil Workers International Union, 1941-1949, undated (Box 33)
  - Oil Workers International Union: Constitutions, 1942-1953 (Box 33)
  - Oil Workers International Union: Local 381, 1939 (Box 33)
  - Oil Workers International Union: Local 449 (Texas City, TX), 1942 (Box 33)
  - One Big Union (Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada), 1923 (Box 33)
  - Ontario Federation of Labour, 1952 (Box 33)
  - Ontario Public Service Employees Union (Canada), 1981 (Box 33)
  - Operative Mule Spinners of Fall River and District (Fall River, MA), 1886 (Box 33)
  - Operative Plasterers' and Cement Finishers' International Association of the United States and Canada, 1922 (Box 33)
  - Operative Plasterers' and Cement Finishers' International Association of the United States and Canada, 1953-1972 (Box 33)
  - Operative Plasterers' and Cement Masons' International Association of the United States and Canada: Constitutions, 1920-1975 (Box 33)
  - Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1904-1962 (Box 33)
  - Order of Railroad Telegraphers: Constitutions, 1942-1960 (Box 33)
  - Order of Railroad Conductors of America, 1884, 1919, 1954 (Box 33)
  - Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen, 1960-1966 (Box 33)
  - Order of Sleeping Car Conductors, 1937 (Box 33)
  - Oregon State Employees Association, 1977 (Box 33)
  - Organizacion Regional Interamericana de Trabajadores (O.R.I.T.), 1965 (Box 33)
- P, 1920-2008; 2.5 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons and 1 manuscript box
  - Pacific Coast Marine Firemen, Oilers, Watertenders and Wipers Association, 1948 (Box 33)
  - Pacific Coast Marine Firemen, Oilers, Watertenders and Wipers Association, 1960, 1977 (Box 33)
  - Packinghouse Workers Organizing Committee, 1941 (Box 33)
  - Pan-American Federation of Labor, 1929, undated (Box 33)
  - Paper, Allied-Industrial, Chemical and Energy Workers International Union, 1999 (Box 33)
  - Paper Workers Organizing Committee, 1944 (Box 33)
  - Pattern Makers' League of North America, 1932-1962, undated (Box 33)
  - Paving Cutters' Union of the U.S.A. and Canada, 1948 (Box 33)
  - Perth Electric Tramway Workers (Australia), 1930 (Box 33)
  - Philadelphia Transportation Company Strike of 1943, 1944 (Box 33)
  - Physicians National Housestaff Association, 1975-1976, undated (Box 33)